I don't want to walk anymore!
Pull yourself together!
I don't wanna!
Piggyback!
Hey, Inaba, could you help me out here?
Taichi!
Her desires got unleashed!
Don't care. Handle it yourself.
Inaba!
Hey!
Could you stop fooling around?
Yaegashi-kun, if you use this field trip as cover to do anything weird to Nagase-san, I'll have your head.
Don't make me sound like a bad guy!
Taichi!
Piggyback!
Isn't there something in your heart that's just as important?
Nagase, quit it!
Hey, Inaba, help me!
Inaba!
Having to use this old equipment is making me one hell of an angry camper.
Sorry. It's my fault for losing at rock-paper-scissors.
Well, we can't change the past.
You need to make it up to us somehow.
Watase-kun, could you think of something for us?
With pleasure!
You're enjoying this.
It's okay.
This kind of stuff makes for good memories later on.
Right, Inaban?
I don't need memories of doing crap that I didn't need to.
Um... I'm sorry.
How are you so bad at rock-paper-scissors?
You lost against Iori and Watase in every game.
I got the worst luck on this morning's TV horoscope.
That might have something to do with it.
Whoa.
You'd probably die if you fell from here.
Be careful, Mr. Misfortune.
You'd have to go out of your way to actually fall from here.
What are you smiling for?
You were all depressed just a second ago.
No reason. It feels like it's been a while since we talked like this.
What? It's not a bad thing.
Shut up.
I wonder how those three are doing.
They should be just fine.
I mean, it looks like Inaba-chan is almost back to normal.
More importantly, about that apron...
It looks great on you!
Man, long hair and an apron make an absolutely divine combination!
Sometimes I'm amazed at how laid-back you can be.
Were you born this way or what?
You're good at this, Nagase.
I cook a lot at home, you know.
I see.
And Inaba... could be better.
Crap!
Don't underestimate me!
When I get in the zone, I'm freaking crazy!
Need me to show you?
D-Did I strike a chord?
An unleashed desire?
And Iori, don't think you've won just because Taichi said that!
Why is this about me now?
Let's see who can cut these things faster!
D-Do I have to do it, too?
Don't ask me.
We're done washing the rice.
Oh, looks like you've made up.
Putting you in the same group was the right idea.
You can't be serious.
Isn't that long enough, Fujishima-san?
I'm starving.
No.
Just a little longer.
Why can't we eat now?
All the other groups are eating already!
A little more.
I'm adding the last bit of my own original spice.
Huh?
I didn't know you were so finicky when it came to food.
Not all the time.
Just when it involves curry.
Why?!
Okay, it's time.
It's good!
The greatest spice is hunger—I mean, love!
Hey, are you listening?
It's too good! I can't hear you!
I'm listening!
Love, right? Love!
Um...
I hope the love you're talking about isn't that kind.
Who knows?
By the way, Nagase-san...
There's rice on your cheek.
D-Don't!
I'll get it myself.
What a shame.
Let's focus on eating, okay?
That was so good!
Yeah.
I'd go on a field trip every day for this!
Sure.
Hey, Inaban—
Wait, Inaba! Are you bleeding?
Look! Right here!
Oh, I didn't notice.
How could you not?
What if it gets infected?
I can take care of myself!
Anyone have a band-aid?
Oh, shut up.
I brought my own.
I'll go with her.
Wait, Nagase...
Just mind your own business...
Wh-What is it, Iori?
Inaban, are you...
Are you in love with...
Wait, Inaban!
She found out!
I wonder where those two went.
Inaban!
Hey!
Why?
Inaban!
Tell me... why?
Are you... in love with Taichi... too?
Why?
You kept trying to get me and Taichi together.
I mean, I knew you loved Taichi, too...
But I thought it was just as a friend.
Why did you want to get me and Taichi together?
Were you just going to let me have him?
Inaban...
You are going to tell me why right now, Inaba Himeko!
Iori, did your—
Tell me!
Tell me! Tell me right now!
If you won't, then we're no longer friends!
Because...
Because if I didn't, we couldn't stay together!
Why wouldn't we be able to?!
Because... when it comes to guys and girls...
if love and stuff got mixed in, we'd be bound to fight.
Our friendship wouldn't even stand a chance.
Aoki loves Yui,
and in spite of what Yui says, everyone knows she feels the same way.
You were looking for someone who would support you,
and that's like second nature to Taichi.
If you and Taichi got together, everything would be just peachy!
If that happened, we'd stay together forever.
That's just stupid.
Just because everything would be peachy?
I didn't know that Inaba Himeko was this stupid.
I was always alone.
Always, always alone.
But then I got to high school, and I finally met people I could call my friends.
I didn't want to lose them, no matter what.
I didn't know what else to do!
You think I'd know that?
If you're lonely, then tell someone!
If you're anxious, then tell someone!
The world isn't made of people who can analyze others like you can!
If you want people to know something, you need to tell them!
Embarrassed or worried or whatever, just tell them!
You think I could?!
If I showed any sign of weakness, no one would need me anymore.
I didn't have a choice!
Tell me, what could I have done?!
You didn't need to do anything!
That's not true!
A person like me... An awful, horrible person—
Don't call yourself a horrible person!
Don't talk about yourself like that!
I can't help it!
I'm not a good person like the rest of you!
How is that supposed to make me feel since I love you for who you are!
I love you, Inaban.
I really love you.
If you won't believe me, I'll say it until you do.
And it's not just me. Everyone loves you.
But that's not the real me.
That's the strong, infallible Inaba Himeko.
I'll love you no matter how weak you are.
You're wrong.
You're wrong, Inaban.
You're a better person than you think.
No, that's wrong, too.
There aren't any "good" or "bad" people. You can't just slap a label on people like that.
Trust me.
If you think...
If you think that I'm a good person, then trust me!
You have my word!
Don't worry, Inaban.
You don't need to do anything crazy.
I'll always be your friend.
No, that's not exactly right.
I'll always want to be your friend!
Please! Let me be your friend!
I...
I've always wanted someone to tell me that.
But it's too late now.
I'd just get in the way of you and Taichi.
I don't want to ruin the CRC.
So I can't go back to the club room.
Why?
Why can't you go back?
Because everything would be way too awkward.
I just can't.
Inaban, you said that if Taichi and I got together, everything would be just peachy.
But if you and Taichi got together,
wouldn't everything be just peachy then, too?
But you and Taichi make a good couple,
and I didn't even care much for Taichi at first, either.
Wait, I still don't—
How can you lie to yourself like that?!
I'm not lying.
I know you're trying to do everything you can to keep the five of us together,
but now you love Taichi so much that you just can't take it anymore.
The Inaba Himeko I know would do whatever it took to keep both!
No matter how bad it got, she'd never give up.
Arrogant to the end, with no respect for anyone,
controlling people for her own benefit and getting her way no matter what it takes!
That's Inaba Himeko!
And even if you get your way,
the friendship between Nagase Iori and Inaba Himeko won't end over one lousy guy!
That's what I believe.
So you can come back to the club room worry-free.
Okay, I got it.
Don't come crying to me if you don't like it.
Don't underestimate me, either!
If that's how you want it, I'll make my victory a flawless one.
There won't even be a hair on his head left for you.
Sorry, but I don't plan on losing or giving him to you.
You really think you can beat me?
There are plenty of ways to beat a girl who's got nothing but being cute going for her.
That's mean!
You were really emotional just now.
I wonder if that's the real me.
Wait, when did my desires stop being un—
Iori?
Hello.
I hope you don't get the wrong idea.
Don't give me that bullshit.
What the hell are you doing here?!
I wanted to tell you that this desire unleashing phenomenon is about to end.
End? So it's all over now?
But there was a little accident.
I thought it might be interesting—
I mean, best if I told you.
You're not making any sense!
Yaegashi-san fell.
Huh?
He fell.
Yaegashi-san fell.
Fell?
You don't mean... from there?!
Taichi! Taichi! Taichi!
It's a bit different from Nagase-san's case.
I didn't do anything this time.
What did you call it?
Being a selfless freak?
It's quite something.
Ow...
Don't make us worry like that!
We freaked out and ran all the way here!
Yeah! Yui and I were having a great time cleaning up together!
That doesn't matter.
Oh, Inaba?
What's wrong? You're all red.
Wasn't Nagase-san with you?
Can you believe it? Taichi went and did something stupid again.
He tried to help a kitten that got stuck in a tree.
And then he fell from there.
How's the cat?
Just fine.
It doesn't look like she got injured. She'll be fine.
That goes for you, too.
Sorry for worrying you.
Seriously. You're always making us worry about you.
At least we can look back on this and laugh.
Inaba?
What's wrong, Inaba?
Don't make me worry, you idiot!
You didn't have to hit me so hard.
Sorry!
Don't cry!
I don't know what I did, but I'm sorry!
I apologize!
So stop crying!
Inaba, don't cry.
Okay? Taichi's fine.
Were you that worried about him?
You don't need to cry.
You don't need to cry, Inaba-chan.
I finally made it back.
Iori, where were you?
I don't know where I was, either.
Wait, what happened to Inaban?
Your guess is as good as ours.
Inaba, I don't know what I did, but I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
Inaba, you don't need to cry.
Taichi's just fine, Inaba-chan.
Inaban? Inaban?
What's wrong?
So the whole "desire unleashing" thing is finally over?
It's going to be hell trying to catch up with work on the paper.
But is it really over?
Yeah.
If something else comes up...
There's no point in worrying about that.
What's important is that we're free right now. Let's enjoy it!
Seriously, how does someone end up as laid-back as you?
Where are Taichi and Inaba-chan?
Oh, I think Fujishima-san is giving them an earful for what they did.
Maybe.
Then I guess...
...we should go home first.
Hey, Inaba.
You wanted to talk to me about something?
Wh-What is it?
I love you.
Um... Er...
Uh...
I-I...
I'm...
I'm really happy that you feel that way about me.
I consider it an honor, from the bottom of my heart.
But right now, I'm in love with Nagase.
I know that.
But "right now" means that I have a chance to turn that around.
Uh... that's not exactly what I—
I mean, you're not going out with Iori yet.
Getting between you is easy enough.
Oh, and I told Iori that I'd be confessing to you.
So don't worry.
It's going to be a fair race to the finish.
No need to mind either of us.
Just go about your business as usual.
W-Wait! You're way ahead of me here.
What do you mean?
It sounds like you and Nagase are going to fight over—
You did it to me once before.
Turnabout's fair play, right?
I'm going to the club room tomorrow.
See you.
Shoot!
My heart!
I kissed him!
See you.
Himeko, what happened? You never say anything when you leave.
Shut up, stupid.